Finding Aid for Inter-House Assembly (University of Michigan) records, 1950-1970
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Inter-House Assembly (University of Michigan) records 1950-1970
University of Michigan. Inter-House Assembly.
12 linear feet and 3 oversize volumes
87205 BImu Bimu F44 2
Records, 1950-1970,of the Inter-House Assembly of the University of Michigan that served as an association of dormitory representatives. The records contain notebooks, reports and scrapbooks relating to the programs and activities of the University's dormitories.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were received from donor no. 5173.
The record group is open without restriction.
Established in 1948, the Inter-House Council was an organization drawn from the governing bodies of the University's men's residence halls. The Inter-Quadrangle Council succeeded this organization in 1960. The Assembly Association, established in 1955, was the governing organization for the women’s residence halls. In 1966,the two organizations merged to form the Inter-House Assembly.
The records contain notebooks, reports and scrapbooks relating to the programs and activities of the University's dormitories.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. Assembly Association.; University of Michigan. Inter-House Assembly.; University of Michigan. Inter-House Council.; University of Michigan. Student Government Council.; University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs--1951-1960.; University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs--1961-1970.; University of Michigan--Student housing.; Dormitories--Michigan--Ann Arbor.
Genre Terms:
Scrapbooks.
- Notebooks
  - Inter-House Council, 1950-1960 (Box 1)
  - Inter-Quadrangle Council, 1960-1965 (Box 1)
  - Inter-Quadrangle Council, 1960-1965 (cont.) (Box 2)
  - Inter-House Assembly, 1966-1968 (Box 2)
  - Big Ten Residence Hall Conference, 1955-1959 (Box 2)
  - Assembly Association, 1955-1962 (Box 3)
  - Assembly Dormitory Council, 1955-1962 (Box 3)
  - Assembly House Council, 1964-1966 (Box 4)
  - Dormitory Visitation Policies, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous Dormitory Policies, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Food Service, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Pre-Marital and Marital Counseling Services, 1966 (Box 4)
- Papers
  - Inter-House Assembly, 1966-1970 (Box 5)
  - Inter-House Assembly, 1966-1970 (cont.) (Box 6)
  - Inter-House Assembly, 1966-1970 (cont.) (Box 7)
  - Inter-House Assembly, 1966-1970 (cont.) (Box 8)
  - Inter-Quadrangle Council (Box 8)
  - Inter-House Council, 1950-1960 (Box 9)
  - Assembly Association, 1955-1966 (Box 9)
  - Assembly Association, 1955-1966 (cont.) (Box 10)
  - Assembly Association, 1955-1966 (cont.) (Box 11)
  - Housing Policy Board, 1971 (Box 12)
  - Student Government Council, 1957-1962 and 1968-1969 (Box 12)
- Financial Ledgers
  - Association of Independent Men, 1938-1940 (Box 12)
  - 1955-1956 (Box 12)
- Scrapbooks
  - Michigan League, 1938-1940, (outsize (Volume 1)
  - Assembly Association
    - 1957-1962, (outsize (Volume 2)
    - 1963-1964, (outsize (Volume 3)